Guide to the Christopher Tunnard Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE AND TOPICAL FILES, 1921-1978; Series I; 11 linear feet (26 boxes)
  - Regional planning, undated (Box 16, Folder 257)
  - Regional Planning Agency of South Central Connecticut, 1960-1966 Dec, undated (Box 16, Folder 258-259)
  - Reilly, Charles, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 260)
  - Rice, James, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 261)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1951, 1956-1958 (Box 17, Folder 262-264)
  - Saa - Sax (Box 17, Folder 265)
  - Sc - Sei (Box 17, Folder 266)
  - Sem - Si (Box 17, Folder 267)
  - Sk - Sp (Box 17, Folder 268)
  - Sta - Sti (Box 17, Folder 269)
  - Sto - Sy (Box 17, Folder 270)
  - St. Augustine, Florida, 1958, 1965-1967, undated (Box 17, Folder 271)
  - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies (Salzburg, Austria), 1966-1971 (Box 17, Folder 272)
  - Saratoga National Historic Park, 1968, undated (Box 17, Folder 273)
  - Save the Park Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 17, Folder 274)
  - Sawyer, Charles, 1952-1956 (Box 17, Folder 275)
  - Scenic Roads Conference, 1966-1968, undated (Box 17, Folder 276-277)
  - Scholarships, fellowships, and prizes, 1952-1961, undated (Box 18, Folder 278)
  - Shillaber, Caroline, 1957-1959, undated (Box 18, Folder 279)
  - Society of Architectural Historians, 1952-1967, undated (Box 18, Folder 280-282)
  - Stevenson, Eric, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 283)
  - Stevenson, Frederic R., 1955, undated (Box 18, Folder 284)
  - Sweet, Gordon, 1957-1960 (Box 18, Folder 285)
  - Ta - Th (Box 18, Folder 286)
  - Ti - Ty (Box 18, Folder 287)
  - Thiel, Philip, 1959, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 288)
  - Toll, Seymour I., 1955-1957, 1964-1968, undated (Box 18, Folder 289)
  - Ul - University B (Box 18, Folder 290)
  - University C - University R (Box 18, Folder 291)
  - University T - Up (Box 18, Folder 292)
  - UNESCO
    - General, 1961-1975, undated (Box 18, Folder 293-294)
    - Jamaica mission, 1963-1969, undated (Box 19, Folder 295-297)
    - Jamaica mission, undated (Box 19, Folder 298)
    - Kathmandu Valley, Nepal mission, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 299-303)
    - Kathmandu Valley, Nepal mission, 1976, undated (Box 19, Folder 304)
    - Kathmandu Valley, Nepal mission, undated (Box 20, Folder 305-306)
    - Published reports on cultural missions, 1966-1971 (Box 20, Folder 307-310)
  - Union College, 1964, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 311)
  - United States Housing and Home Financing Agency, 1956-1960 (Box 20, Folder 312)
  - University of California at Berkeley, 1957-1966, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 313)
  - University of Chicago, 1951, 1962-1967 (Box 20, Folder 314)
  - University of Manitoba, 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 315)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1953-1963, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 316)
  - Urban History Group, 1959-1964, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 317)
  - Urban planning: printed material, 1921, 1925, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 318)
  - Urban planning: printed material, 1947-1961 (Box 21, Folder 319-321)
  - Urban planning: printed material, 1963, 1968-1974, 1976, undated (Box 21, Folder 322-323)
  - Urban renewal, 1955-1957 (Box 21, Folder 324)
  - V (Box 21, Folder 325)
  - Voight Memorial Planting, 1953-1955, undated (Box 21, Folder 326)
  - W - Wer (Box 21, Folder 327)
  - Wes - Wh (Box 21, Folder 328)
  - Wi - Wu (Box 21, Folder 329)
  - Weinberg, Robert C., 1954-1963, undated (Box 21, Folder 330)
  - Wethersfield, Connecticut, 1960-1964, undated (Box 22, Folder 331)
  - Weybright, Victor
    See also: box 13, folder 243
  - Wheaton, William L. C., 1957-1959, undated (Box 22, Folder 332)
  - Who's Who in America, 1952-1957 (Box 22, Folder 333)
  - Wilder, Amos Tappan, 1968, 1973-1974, undated (Box 22, Folder 334)
  - Wilder, Amos Tappan, undated (Box 22, Folder 335)
  - Wildlife preserves
    See also: box 14, folder 243
  - Williams, Norman, 1954-1959, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 336)
  - Wood, Richardson, 1953-1960, 1963-1966, undated (Box 22, Folder 337-338)
  - Woodbury, Coleman, 1955, 1960, 1965-1966, undated (Box 22, Folder 339-340)
  - World Design Conference (Tokyo, Japan), 1955, 1959-1960, undated (Box 22, Folder 341)
  - World Society for Ekistics, 1973-1974, undated (Box 22, Folder 342)
  - Wylie, Craig
    See also: box 8, folder 128
  - Y - Z (Box 22, Folder 343)
  - Yale University
    - Art and Architecture
      - Architecture Department
        - Chairman, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 344)
        - Executive Committee, 1952-1958, undated (Box 23, Folder 345-346)
        - Inwood Planning Study: layouts, 1975
          See: box 44, folders 715-717
        - Lecture Committee, 1956-1960 (Box 23, Folder 347)
        - Miscellaneous announcements, memos, and notices, 1950-1960, 1967-1968, undated (Box 23, Folder 348)
        - Parson's Medal, 1952-1959 (Box 23, Folder 349)
      - City Planning
        - Alumni information, 1944-1958, undated (Box 23, Folder 350)
        - Atlantic Urban Region Conference Proceedings, 1955 June-1957, undated (Box 23, Folder 351-354)
        - City Planning: A Pictorial Compendium of Examples and Designs, 1954, undated (Box 23, Folder 355)
          See also: box 46, folder 724
        - City Planning at Yale: A Selection of Papers and Projects, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 356)
        - City Planning at Yale: A Selection of Papers and Projects, 1955-1956, undated (Box 24, Folder 357)
        - Course catalog material, 1953, 1958-1960, undated (Box 24, Folder 358)
        - Educational Role Conference, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 359)
        - Equipment and supplies, 1953-1956, undated (Box 24, Folder 360)
        - Highway Conference, 1966-1968, undated (Box 24, Folder 361)
        - Highway Research Project, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 362)
        - Highway Research Team: Highway as Environment
          - Title page - p. 28, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 363)
          - pp. 29-99, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 364-366)
          - pp. 1-17, 28-52, 66-90, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 367)
          - Titles and captions, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 368)
        - Materials regarding development of program, 1954-1959, 1965-1972, undated (Box 24, Folder 369)
        - Miscellaneous correspondence and administrative material, 1950-1961 (Box 24, Folder 370)
        - Miscellaneous correspondence and administrative material, 1963-1971, undated (Box 24, Folder 371)
        - Project for field study and research on the American tradition in city planning, 1952-1953, undated (Box 24, Folder 372)
        - Proposal for the City Planning Program 1970-1971, 1970-1971, undated (Box 24, Folder 373)
        - Scholarships, prizes, and fellowships, 1946, 1951-1959 (Box 25, Folder 374)
        - Slide lists, 1947, 1956, undated (Box 25, Folder 375)
        - Student enrollment, 1950-1960, 1964, 1968-1970, undated (Box 25, Folder 376)
        - Student field trips, 1952, undated (Box 25, Folder 377)
        - Urban Regional Planning Conference, 1957 February-April 16 (Box 25, Folder 378)
        - Urban Regional Planning Conference, 1957 April 17-Dec, undated (Box 25, Folder 379)
        - Visiting lecturers, 1953-1960, 1970, undated (Box 25, Folder 380)
      - Dean, 1948, 1952-1961, 1965-1969, undated (Box 25, Folder 381-382)
      - Newsletter, 1953-1961, undated (Box 25, Folder 383)
    - Art Gallery, 1954-1958, undated (Box 25, Folder 384)
    - Bureau of Highway Traffic, 1950, 1954-1960, undated (Box 25, Folder 385)
    - Committee on the Course of Study, 1953-1954, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 386)
    - Committee on the Future of Urban Studies at Yale, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 387)
    - Graduate School, 1954-1955, 1959-1970 (Box 25, Folder 388)
    - Law School, 1956-1959 (Box 25, Folder 389)
    - Library, 1950-1959, undated (Box 25, Folder 390)
    - Meyer Committee on Yale's Involvement in Urban, City Planning and Social Problems, 1969 June-Sep, undated (Box 25, Folder 391-392)
    - Miscellaneous, 1952-1958-1960, 1964-1971, 1976, undated (Box 26, Folder 393-394)
    - News Bureau, 1949, 1953-1959, 1966-1967, undated (Box 26, Folder 395)
    - President, 1953, 1958, 1965-1971, undated (Box 26, Folder 396)
    - Provost, 1955-1967, undated (Box 26, Folder 397)
    - Secretary, 1952, 1956-1962, 1966-1967, undated (Box 26, Folder 398)
    - Timothy Dwight College, 1953-1959 (Box 26, Folder 399)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 400)
    - Yale College, 1954-1956 (Box 26, Folder 401)
    - "Yale Reports" radio broadcast, 1955-1959, undated (Box 26, Folder 402)
  - Yale University Press, 1953-1954, 1958-1964, 1973-1974, 1978, undated (Box 26, Folder 403)
  - Fragments, undated (Box 26, Folder 404)
  - Unidentified, 1951-1968, 1975, undated (Box 26, Folder 405)
- WRITINGS, 1949-1974; Series II; 3 linear feet (7 boxes)
  This series contains four subseries: Books, Articles, Reviews, and Speeches and Lectures. Each subseries is arranged alphabetically by title. Reviews are alphabetized by the title of the book reviewed. Miscellaneous notes, outlines, and unidentified materials follow the four subseries.
  - Books
    - American Skyline
      - Illustrations and captions, undated (Box 27, Folder 406)
      - Notes, undated (Box 27, Folder 407)
      - Outlines, undated (Box 27, Folder 408-411)
      - Typescript
        - pp. 1-52, undated (Box 27, Folder 412)
        - pp. 53-103, undated (Box 27, Folder 413)
        - pp. 104-156, undated (Box 27, Folder 414)
        - pp. 157-201, undated (Box 27, Folder 415)
        - pp. 202-253, undated (Box 27, Folder 416)
        - pp. 254-300 and index, undated (Box 27, Folder 417)
        - Drafts, undated (Box 27, Folder 418-420)
        - Drafts, undated (Box 28, Folder 421-427)
        - Outline and draft
          - Title page-p. 50, undated (Box 28, Folder 428)
          - pp. 51-100, undated (Box 28, Folder 429)
          - pp. 101-147, undated (Box 28, Folder 430)
          - pp. 148-199, undated (Box 28, Folder 431)
          - pp. 200-244, undated (Box 28, Folder 432)
          - pp. 245-300, undated (Box 28, Folder 433)
        - pp. 301-335 and bibliography, undated (Box 28, Folder 434)
    - A Brief History of New York: outline, undated (Box 28, Folder 435)
    - The City of Man
      - Notes, undated (Box 28, Folder 436)
      - Typescript
        - Introductory material and pp. 92-121, 1952 January 8 (Box 28, Folder 437)
        - pp. 122-334, 1952 January 8 (Box 28, Folder 438)
        - pp. 335-445, pp. 472-549, 1952 January 8 (Box 28, Folder 439)
        - Foreward, pp. i-vi, pp. 55-58, pp. 122-198, undated (Box 28, Folder 440)
        - pp. 199-321, undated (Box 29, Folder 441)
        - pp. 322-387, undated (Box 29, Folder 442)
        - pp. 388-509, undated (Box 29, Folder 443)
        - pp. 510-549, undated (Box 29, Folder 444)
    - The Creation of Cities: outline, undated (Box 29, Folder 445)
    - The English Park: notes, undated (Box 29, Folder 446)
    - How to Look at Cities: outline, undated (Box 29, Folder 447)
    - Man-Made America
      - Fragments, undated (Box 29, Folder 448)
      - Typescript
        - pp. 1-45, undated (Box 29, Folder 449)
        - Draft
          - pp. 1-105, pp.26-35, unnumbered pages, undated (Box 29, Folder 450)
          - Unnumbered pages, undated (Box 29, Folder 451)
    - A World With a View
      - Galley, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 452)
      - Illustrations, captions, and notes, 1977, undated (Box 29, Folder 453)
      - Illustrations, captions, and notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 454)
      - Proof
        - pp. i-ix, pp. 1-51, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 455)
        - pp. 52-109, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 456)
        - pp. 122-193, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 457)
      - Proofed draft
        - Table of contents, pp. 1-41, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 458)
        - pp. 42-102, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 459)
        - pp. 103-148, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 460)
        - pp. 149-211, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 461)
        - pp. 212-249, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 462)
      - Revised proof
        - pp. i-xii, pp. 1-50, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 463)
        - pp. 51-112, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 464)
        - pp. 113-179, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 465)
        - pp. 180-196, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 466)
      - Typescript
        - pp. i-iv, pp. 1-39, undated (Box 30, Folder 467)
        - pp. 40-77, undated (Box 31, Folder 468)
        - pp. 78-135, undated (Box 31, Folder 469)
        - pp. 136-208, undated (Box 31, Folder 470)
        - pp. i, iii, v, viii, xi-xvi, pp. 1-57, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 471)
        - pp. 58-99, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 472)
        - pp. 100-145, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 473)
        - pp. 146-199, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 474)
        - Footnotes, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 475)
      - Volume, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 476)
  - Articles
    - "American Townscape", undated (Box 31, Folder 477)
    - "America's Super Cities" (Harper's article), 1958 August (Box 31, Folder 478)
    - "The Architecture of the Regional Landscape", 1954 February (Box 31, Folder 479)
    - "An Artist in the Streets", 1953 February (Box 31, Folder 480)
    - "The Challenge of America's Hideous Wasteland", undated (Box 31, Folder 481)
    - "Cities for Men to Live In", undated (Box 31, Folder 482)
    - "Citizens All: The Case for Urban Regional Planning"
      - Manuscript draft and notes, undated (Box 31, Folder 483)
      - Typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 484)
      - Typescript draft, undated (Box 31, Folder 485)
    - "The City and Its Interpreters", 1961 November (Box 32, Folder 486)
    - "A City Called Beautiful", undated (Box 32, Folder 487)
    - "The Conscious Stone", 1954 December (Box 32, Folder 488)
    - "Design at the Scale of the Region", 1967 January (Box 32, Folder 489)
    - "The Development of American Architecture and Building", undated (Box 32, Folder 490)
    - "A Few Ragged Huts", undated (Box 32, Folder 491)
    - "Fire on the Prairie", 1952 (Box 32, Folder 492)
    - "The Garden of the Silver Pavilion", undated (Box 32, Folder 493)
    - [Historic Preservation], undated (Box 32, Folder 494)
    - "Impressions of Tokyo", [1961?] (Box 32, Folder 495)
    - "In Search of a City", undated (Box 32, Folder 496)
    - "The International Center for the Study of the Preservation and Restoration of Cultural Property", undated (Box 32, Folder 497)
    - "The Landscape of the Big Street", 1956 July (Box 32, Folder 498)
    - El tratamiento dietético de la insufficiencia cardíaca, undated (Box 32, Folder 499)
    - "The Natural City", undated (Box 32, Folder 500)
    - "The Open-Ended City", undated (Box 32, Folder 501)
    - "Planning as a Profession", undated (Box 32, Folder 502)
    - "The Planning Syndrome in Western Culture", 1973 January (Box 32, Folder 503)
    - "The Preservation of the Cultural Patrimony", undated (Box 32, Folder 504)
    - "Prospect for the Countryside", undated (Box 32, Folder 505)
    - "Rearing the Federal City", undated (Box 32, Folder 506)
    - "Recommendations Concerning the Development of Calf Pasture Beach Park and the Shady Beach Area in Norwalk, Connecticut", 1952 October (Box 32, Folder 507)
    - "The Regional City", undated (Box 32, Folder 508)
    - "Scene", undated (Box 32, Folder 509)
    - "A Study of Tourism in New England", undated (Box 32, Folder 510)
    - "Super City on the Seaboard", [1958?] (Box 32, Folder 511)
    - "Taste and Social Change", 1966 May (Box 32, Folder 512)
    - "Too Fast, Too Far", 1960 (Box 32, Folder 513)
    - Traffic Quarterly article, undated (Box 32, Folder 514)
    - "What Kind of Landscape for the New Towns?", undated (Box 32, Folder 515)
    - Articles, fragments of, undated (Box 32, Folder 516-519)
    - Articles, incomplete, undated (Box 33, Folder 520-521)
  - Reviews
    - C-M, 1951, 1954, 1961-1962, undated (Box 33, Folder 522)
    - O-Z, 1949-1961, 1970, undated (Box 33, Folder 523)
  - Speeches and Lectures
    - "The Bees of Aristaeous", undated (Box 33, Folder 524)
    - "Can Planning Stop the Destruction of Our Landscape?", 1958 October (Box 33, Folder 525)
    - "Cities by Design", undated (Box 33, Folder 526)
    - Comments made during appearance on "Yale Interprets the News", 1953 September 27 (Box 33, Folder 527)
    - "Historic Districts: Ghosts and Intruders", 1964 (Box 33, Folder 528)
    - "How to Build a Better Looking New York?", 1955 May (Box 33, Folder 529)
    - "Interurbia", 1957 October (Box 33, Folder 530)
    - "Melcarth Lecture", undated (Box 33, Folder 531)
    - National Book Council Award Acceptance Speech, undated (Box 33, Folder 532)
    - "Our Urban Waterfronts: A Second Chance", 1965 May 24 (Box 33, Folder 533)
    - "The Raking Glance", 1958 December 6 (Box 33, Folder 534)
    - "The Roads We Travel", undated (Box 33, Folder 535)
    - "Sharawadji Reconsidered", 1975 April 16 (Box 33, Folder 536)
    - "Should We Revive the City Beautiful?", 1953 October (Box 33, Folder 537)
    - Speech given at Williamsburg, Virginia, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 538)
    - Speech given to Yale Alumni, 1957 April 6 (Box 33, Folder 539)
    - [Town Planning], 1954 (Box 33, Folder 540)
    - "Urbanism, Art, and Life", undated (Box 33, Folder 541)
    - "Walter Gropius at Harvard", 1962 (Box 33, Folder 542)
    - "What's Wrong with Urban Design?", 1963 (Box 33, Folder 543)
  - Notes, miscellaneous, undated (Box 33, Folder 544-545)
  - Outlines, miscellaneous, undated (Box 33, Folder 546)
  - Unidentified bibliography and index galley, undated (Box 33, Folder 547)
- TEACHING FILES, 1947-1975; Series III; 3 linear feet (7 boxes)
  This series contains three subseries: Courses, Topics, and Student Papers. Each subseries is arranged alphabetically. Folders containing examinations and miscellaneous teaching notes follow the Topics subseries.
  - Courses
    - American Regionalism (Box 34, Folder 548)
    - Civic Art (Box 34, Folder 549-554)
    - Environmental Quality (Box 34, Folder 555-559)
    - Environmental Quality (Box 35, Folder 560-566)
    - History of City Planning and Urban Design (Box 35, Folder 567-569)
    - History of Urban Form (Box 35, Folder 570-573)
    - History of Urban Form (Box 36, Folder 574-585)
    - Introduction to Planning (Box 36, Folder 586-592)
    - Introduction to Planning (Box 37, Folder 593-598)
    - Landscape Architecture (Box 37, Folder 599-601)
    - Metropolitan Area Planning (Box 37, Folder 602-603)
    - Planning Projects (Box 37, Folder 604)
    - Preservation Planning (Box 37, Folder 605)
    - Seminar on the City (Box 37, Folder 606)
    - Study of the City (Box 37, Folder 607)
    - University of Wisconsin Seminars (Box 37, Folder 608)
    - Urban Studies Seminar (Box 37, Folder 609)
    - Urban Theory (Box 38, Folder 610)
    - Utopia and Para-utopia (Box 38, Folder 611)
  - Topics
    - Alberti (Box 38, Folder 612)
    - American Renaissance (Box 38, Folder 613)
    - Ancient City Planning (Box 38, Folder 614)
    - Colonization (Box 38, Folder 615)
    - Dark Ages (Box 38, Folder 616)
    - Early Renaissance (Box 38, Folder 617)
    - Esthetic Theory (Box 38, Folder 618)
    - Federal City (Box 38, Folder 619)
    - France (Box 38, Folder 620)
    - Gardens (Box 38, Folder 621)
    - Leningrad (Box 38, Folder 622)
    - Megaform (Box 38, Folder 623)
    - Metropolitan Improvement: Paris and New York (Box 38, Folder 624)
    - Neo-classic (Box 38, Folder 625)
    - New Towns (Box 38, Folder 626)
    - Nineteenth Century American Cities (Box 38, Folder 627)
    - Plato (Box 38, Folder 628)
    - Rome (Box 38, Folder 629)
    - Squares: High Renaissance (Box 38, Folder 630)
    - Taste (Box 38, Folder 631)
    - Villes Neuves (Box 39, Folder 632)
  - Examinations (Box 39, Folder 633)
  - Notes, miscellaneous (Box 39, Folder 634-637)
  - Student papers
    - Al-Jalili, Naman, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 638)
    - Alschuler, Frank S., 1947 January 10 (Box 39, Folder 639)
    - Anonymous, undated (Box 39, Folder 640)
    - Barratt, P.J.H., 1961 May 29 (Box 39, Folder 641)
    - Block, Steven, 1961 February 3 (Box 39, Folder 642)
    - Christensen, Donald J., 1969 January (Box 39, Folder 643)
    - Comey, Ralph, undated (Box 39, Folder 644)
    - Day, Norman G. A., 1948 March 20 (Box 39, Folder 645)
    - Ericson, J. E., 1956 October 1 (Box 39, Folder 646)
    - Euston, Andrew F., [1956 September 31] (Box 39, Folder 647)
    - Finney, C. Roger, 1972 May 12 (Box 39, Folder 648)
    - Greenberg, Allan, undated (Box 39, Folder 649)
    - Ho, Tao, 1961 January 11 (Box 40, Folder 650)
    - Hofe, Dean F., undated (Box 40, Folder 651)
    - Hufnagel Karen and Votava, Bob, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 652)
    - Isler, Morton L., 1955 March (Box 40, Folder 653)
    - Jacobson, Richard, 1975 April 14 (Box 40, Folder 654)
    - Jenkins, Thomas H., 1961 May (Box 40, Folder 655)
    - Krauskopf, Jack, 1961 May (Box 40, Folder 656)
    - Kristopeit, Thomas E., undated (Box 40, Folder 657)
    - Lesieur, Gilles J., undated (Box 40, Folder 658)
    - Montes, Gregory, 1972, undated (Box 40, Folder 659)
    - Moore, Allan, 1956 September 31 (Box 40, Folder 660)
    - Ovington, T. M., undated (Box 40, Folder 661)
    - Perlman, Konrad J., 1960 May 4 (Box 40, Folder 662)
    - Peterson, Bo E., 1963 January 14 (Box 40, Folder 663)
    - Pratomo, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 664)
    - Radford, Colin, 1956 October 1 (Box 40, Folder 665)
    - Rush, Earl H., 1959 (Box 40, Folder 666)
    - Russell, Jacqueline, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 667)
    - Second Year Class, Yale University Graduate Program in City Planning, 1960 January (Box 40, Folder 668)
    - Shapiro, Alexandra, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 669)
    - Shepard, Paul H., 1953-1954, undated (Box 40, Folder 670)
    - Sielaff, Bruce W., 1956 October 1 (Box 40, Folder 671)
    - Vare, Edwin, 1956 September 31 (Box 40, Folder 672)
    - Warburton, Ralph, 1961 February 25 (Box 40, Folder 673)
- PICTORIAL MATERIAL, 1907-1977; Series IV; 1.75 linear feet (7 boxes, 1 folio)
  This series contains materials arranged by size and type of material.
  - Photocopied transparencies of New York City area, undated (Box 41, Folder 674)
  - Photographic material
    - [California?], undated (Box 41, Folder 675)
    - Germany and France, undated (Box 41, Folder 676-677)
    - Italy, undated (Box 41, Folder 678)
    - Java, undated (Box 41, Folder 679-680)
    - Negatives, miscellaneous, 1977 May 3, undated (Box 41, Folder 681-682)
    - Paris: rue Etienne Marcel, undated (Box 41, Folder 683)
    - Phillipines, 1907-1910, 1913-1914, undated (Box 41, Folder 684-687)
    - Phillipines, undated (Box 42, Folder 688-689)
    - Photographs miscellaneous, undated (Box 42, Folder 690)
    - Photographs and drawings, miscellaneous, 1964, 1970, 1975, undated (Box 42, Folder 691-694)
    - Photographs with captions for unidentified publication, undated (Box 42, Folder 695)
    - proof sheets, miscellaneous, undated (Box 42, Folder 696-697)
    - Strip mine land reclamation, 1968-1971 (Box 42, Folder 698)
    - Tunnard family photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 699)
    - Tunnard individual and group photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 700)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 42, Folder 701)
  - A World With a View: illustrative material, 1977 March 3, [1977 March 22?], 1977 Apr, 1977-1978, undated (Box 42, Folder 702-707)
  - A World With a View: illustrative material, undated (Box 43, Folder 708-714)
  - Oversize
    - Inwood Planning Study: layouts, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 715-717)
      See also: box 44, folders 715-717
    - San Juan, Puerto Rico capitol building and grounds: photographs and drawings, 1925, 1926, undated (Box 45, Folder 718-720)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, prints and drawings, 1913-1914, undated 1919, undated, 1920, 1924, 1933 (Box 46, Folder 721-723)
    - City Planning: A Pictorial Compendium of Examples and Designs, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 724)
      See also: box 23, folder 355
    - Washington, D.C. capitol building and grounds: photographs and drawings, 1927, undated 1928, 1930, 1931, undated, 1935, undated (Box 47, Folder 725-728)
    - Blueprints
      - Addition and alterations to Tunnard home, 1962 (Folder 48)
      - Foote School, 1957 (Folder 48)